- +91 6353553554
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/harsh-trivediba0752144/
- Rajkot, India

## Harsh Trivedi

## Software Engineer

### SUMMARY

An enthusiastic Software Engineer with almost 2 years of track record of building engineering marvels. My diligent role included daily tasks such as writing multiple lines of code & testing it for various things from automation to web development and also managing a backend team at a startup. I specialise in efficient MEAN, Spring apps, SQL & NoSQL databases that just work across all platforms and browsers. I care deeply about building usable and pleasant things for the most number of people possible. I also love to participate in various hackathons and competitive programming challenges.

#### SKILLS

Springboot Expert

Angular Advanced

NodeJS Expert

Python Advanced

Microsevices Intermediate

Social skills Expert

### LANGUAGES

English Fluent Hindi Fluent

## CERTIFICATES

## Master Microservices with Spring Boot and Spring Cloud

06/2022 - Present

## Java Backend Developer

12/2021 - Present

## PL/SQL Database Programming Learner

09/2021 - Present

# Data structures and algorithm using c++: zero to masters

12/2020 - Present

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### SWE (part-time)

Mercor

02/2022 - Present

- Promoted within 4 months of being an intern to a part-time job position.
- Working as a full stack engineer
- Develop an automation script which automates AWS deployment.
- · Building hiring dashboard
- · Create and support an RDP application service
- My work here is majorly in Nodejs, Java, JS, TS, AWS

## **Backend developer Intern**

**REAL IT SOLUTIONS** 

11/2021 - 05/2022

- Successfully managed a microservice backend with the teams and peers.
- Also was able to add new functionality to backend job schedulers and migrated old registration to OAuth2 for Google and Facebook.
- The majority of my work here was in Java Spring Boot framework with Angular frontend.
- Also built a caching server to make microservices effective with Reddis and Oracle SQL.

## EDUCATION

#### **Computer Science**

Marwadi University

2023

**Bachelor of Computer Science** 

- 16th position in national level hackathon by MLH (Hack4Bengal)
- 9.7/10 GPA
- Built a weather forecast window application with Google and OpenMap APIs information in the Swing framework (Java)

#### Science & humanities

TGES (S.N.K)

2020

High School

- Took part in social activities such as Galaxy Bazar (Mini commerce event all profit is used toward educating girl child)
- Good performance in IPM (Innovative Product Management) event
- Scored 79% in secondary & 70% in high school.